Hey.
What's the matter?
Somebody on the subway
licked my neck-- licked my neck!
Oh! Willy's still alive.
What are you guys
doing?
My mom called. They're going to
run our engagement announcement
in the local paper,
so I'm looking
for a good
picture of us.
Ooh, I'm afraid
that does not exist.
That's not true.
There are great pictures of us.
No, there are great
pictures of you
standing next to a guy
who's going like this.
Oh, my God! That's the creep
that you're with
at the Statue of Liberty!
I don't know what it is.
I just can't take
a good picture.
Hmm, here's a great one.
Yeah. I'm not in that.
I know, but look at me, all tan.
Hey, why don't you guys
go get portraits done
by a professional photographer?
That's a great idea!
I bet they have one
of those wind machines--
you know, like...
( imitating wind )
Yeah, that's great.
Next to that,
Chandler won't look so stupid.
So, Chandler,
what do you say?
All right, but I should
warn you: I'm not going.
I'm going.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Dude, that reverse
lay-up...
Oh! And how about
those three-pointers?
Amazing!
And those guys
were this close
to letting us play
this time, too.
Hey, look, look--
Phoebe's talking to, uh,
"cute coffeehouse guy."
Oh, you guys call him
"Cute Coffeehouse Guy"?
We call him
"Hums While He Pees."
Yes, and we call Ross
"Lingers in the Bathroom."
Hey, you guys?
"Hums While He Pees"
just asked me out.
Wait, I thought
that guy was married.
He is,
but he's getting divorced.
Ross, maybe you know him.
It's not a club.
Phoebe, if this guy's
going through a divorce
is it such a good idea
to start going out with him?
Hey, divorced men
are not bad men.
They have that on the
napkins at the club.
Oh, I got to get
back to work.
You don't have to be back
for a half hour.
Yeah, but my assistant Tag
does sit-ups in the office
during lunch.
( sighing )
Oh, I could just
spread him on a cracker.
Rach, if you have
a crush on this guy,
why would you hire him?
I mean, you know can't
date him, right?
Oh, no, I know that,
I know that...
although we made
a joke, though
that we spend
so much time together
he should call me
his work wife.
Soon he'll be able to call you
"That Lady He Knew
That Got Fired."
I'm not going to get fired
because I'm not going
to act on it.
So, then, you wouldn't mind
if he was dating someone else?
Why? Is he?
He is, isn't he?
He's dating that slut
in marketing.
Maybe I should open
a divorced men's club.
Dude, that's so sad.
I can put a basketball court
in the back.
( laughing )
Could I play?
Oh.
No sit-ups today, Tag?
I just did them.
Oh... Well, drop and give me
ten more.
What?
I-I had a drink with lunch.
Did those, um...
Did those cost reports
come in?
Yeah. I filled them out
last night.
Oh, great. Could you make me
four copies of those?
Sure.
Great. Thank you.
Mmm...
Huh.
Oh...
Hey, Rachel.
( gasping ):
Oh, hi. Hi, Melissa, what's up?
I'm just, uh, I'm just
about to, uh...
go out to the store
and get some stuff
to put in my backpack--
you know, like,
dried fruit
and granola
and stuff like that.
Uh, what's up?
Is Tag here?
No. Why?
Oh, well, I was going
to talk to him about doing
something tonight,
mm-hmm.
You got a little crush
on Tag there, do ya?
Well, we've been flirting
back and forth
but I was hoping tonight
it would turn into something
a little more than that.
Oh, okay. Whoa, whoa,
easy there, Melissa.
This ain't a
locker room, okay?
But, you know,
I remember him saying
that-that he had plans tonight.
Oh, no.
Oh, yeah.
All right, back to work.
Hey, isn't that
Tag's backpack?
Yeah. Melissa, you know,
I don't want to be known
as the, uh, office bitch,
but I will call your supervisor.
Great.
That's great, Monica.
Now, Chandler,
you want to give us
a smile?
Okay.
I'm sorry, is the seat
uncomfortable?
No. I am.
Chandler, sweetie, I know
you can do this, okay?
You have a beautiful smile.
I do?
Yeah!
All right, maybe you
don't have to smile.
Let's try something else.
Let's try, um...
try looking sexy.
Okay.
Or not.
Hi, Joey! What are
you doing here?
Uh, well, I got an audition
down the street
and I spilled sauce all over
the front of my shirt.
You got an extra one?
Yeah, sure.
Uh...
Here.
Great.
You got anything that's
not Ralph Lauren?
Yeah, I-I don't
think so, Joe.
All right, I guess
this'll be fine.
Hey, listen, what are you
doing tonight?
Nothing. Why?
How would you feel about taking
out my assistant, Tag? I'll pay.
Rach, I gotta say,
it's gonna take a lot of money
for me to go out on a date
with a dude.
I'm not asking you to go out
on a date with him.
Really? 'Cause I could kind of
use the money.
Joey, just-just,
he's new in town
and I know he doesn't
have any guy friends.
Just take him to, like,
a ballgame or something.
I'd really appreciate it.
Yeah, okay, sure,
no problem.
Thank you.
Ooh! Hey, doughnuts.
Yeah.
Okay.
I know.
Let's try a look of
far-off wonderment, okay?
We'll gaze into our future
and we'll think
about our marriage
and the days to come.
Chandler, what is the matter
with your face?!
This picture is
supposed to say
"Geller and Bing
to be married"
not "Local woman
saves drowning moron."
( chuckling )
Hey, don't laugh
at him.
He's my drowning moron.
Aw...
That's it! That's it!
Take it, take it.
I like this one.
It seems to say
"I love you, and that's
why I have to kill you.'
They can't all be bad.
Find the one where you
make your bedroom eyes.
Oh, there it is.
Oh, my God, those are
my bedroom eyes?
Why did you ever
sleep with me?
Do you really want to
pull at that thread?
( laughing ):
I'm having
a really good time.
Me, too.
Sorry that guy on the subway
licked your neck.
Oh, no, that's okay.
He's a friend.
Hey, uh, I don't mean
to be presumptuous
but I have
these two tickets
to the Ballroom Dancing
Finals tomorrow night
if you want to go.
Yeah.
I... well, you know,
I missed the semifinals
so I think I would
just be lost.
Look, I know that
it's really lame
but I got these tickets
from my boss, and...
Oh, no, no, no.
My God...
Okay, don't freak out. I'll go.
My ex-wife Whitney
is out there.
I cannot deal with her
right now.
That woman is crazy.
Okay, I know. Hold on.
Hey, Ross?
Yeah?
Um, that's Whitney,
Kyle's ex-wife, out there.
Now, do you think you could,
you know, divert her
so we could slip out?
What?! No.
Well, okay.
But I have two tickets
to the Ballroom Dance Finals...
Look, I don't think so, Pheebs.
( sighing ):
All right, I'll do it.
Oh.
But just because
you're a friend.
Okay.
D-ohh!
Hi, Ginger.
All right, I want my key back.
I don't have it.
It's right there.
( groaning )
Okay, Sherlock.
All right, I'm sorry,
but you'd better go, Pheebs.
All right. I just wanted
to say thank you, though
for diverting Kyle's ex.
Oh, yeah, no, you're welcome.
We'll talk about it later.
Okay.
Hi, Whitney.
Hi, Ross.
You... ready for breakfast?
Yep... oops.
Kyle's ex-wife?
You were supposed to divert her,
not date her.
Hi. I'm sorry.
Can you give me a second
while I talk to this woman
uh, who, by the way,
did not spend the night?
Sure.
Okay.
I did divert her, and we ended
up having a great time, okay?
Watching ballroom dancing?
Yes. That's where we realized
we were both supercool people.
Well, look, okay, Ross.
Kyle just told me some
really bad stuff about her.
Like, like what?
Like she's
really mean
and she's overly critical,
and, and...
no, she will paint a room
a really bright color
without even checking with you.
Okay...?
And she uses sex as a weapon.
Fine. Thank you for warning me.
At breakfast,
I'll be on full alert
for room-painting
and sex weapons.
You're still going
to go out with her?
Yeah!
Well, didn't you hear
what I just said?
Pheebs, come on...
I mean, consider the source.
Of course her ex-husband's
going to say that stuff.
Now, if you'll excuse me...
No, listen to me! She is crazy!
Uh, your door
isn't soundproof.
You see?
Nothing is good enough for her.
Good morning.
Hi, Tag!
So, did you have fun with,
uh, with Joey last night?
Oh, yeah. We went
to the Knicks game.
Oh, that's nice.
Then we went out
to this bar
and he hooked us up
with all these women.
W-women?
You mean, like, old women?
Oh, kind of old, like, 30?
Oh.
And I never used to able
to just talk to girls in bars
but I got, like,
20 phone numbers last night.
Oh, that's great!
Wow, man, so Joey
must have really taught you
some stuff, huh?
A little.
( imitating Joey):
How you doin'?
Joey:
See, that's
a great smile.
Easy, natural...
Now, pretend I have a camera.
You're changing it.
I can't help it.
All right, all right,
all right.
You want to know
what I do
when I take resume shots?
Borrow money from me?
( weak laugh )
Okay, first of all
you want to make it look
spontaneous, right?
Okay, so here's what I do.
I look down...
look down...
keep looking down...
then I look up.
See? All right,
now you try it.
Look down...
you're looking down...
keep looking down...
Why is there jelly
on your shoe?
I had a doughnut.
Hi.
Hey.
So, I heard you had some fun
with Tag
last night.
Yeah, that guy's
all right.
Yeah, and you had fun
teaching him to be all Joey.
What?
You know, all the women.
Hey, you can't teach
someone to be good with women.
That's why I never had
any luck with Chandler.
I'm right here.
Right. Well, would you mind
just not going out with him
again?
Just the idea of you and he
and all these women, it just...
and I know he's my assistant
and I can't date him
ba-la-la... but it just
bothers me, all right?
Hey, no, no, no
you can't take him away
from me.
I got a great partner
to pick up girls with, finally!
I'm still
right here!
All right, will you
at least talk to him
and tell him how hollow
and unsatisfying
this "dating tons of women"
thing is?
What?
I just don't want him
to meet anybody
until I'm over my crush.
And I will get over it.
It's not like I love him.
It's just physical.
But, you know, I mean
I get crushes like this
all the time.
I had a crush on you
when I first met you.
I know. Monica
told me.
Did you have
a crush on me
when you first met me?
Yeah, sure.
Can you people
not see me?
So, will you talk to him?
I don't know, Rach.
Oh, come on.
I'll give you ten
free Ralph Lauren shirts.
One.
No, ten. You said ten.
You can't take that back.
Hey, Joey.
You wanted
to talk to me?
I don't know.
You got something
for me?
Oh, yeah, this is
from Rachel.
Ten...
Okay.
Now, Tag, there's such
a thing as too many women.
Really?
Yeah, for you.
Hey, there you are.
There I am.
You okay?
Yeah. Joey said
I needed to relax
so he gave me
an antihistamine.
What?
Yeah, then I fell asleep
on the subway
and went all the way
to Brooklyn.
Brooklyn is f... far.
Chandler, what
were you thinking?
No, no, but don't worry,
don't worry
because I know how
to take a picture now.
Okay, see?
Look down...
You look down...
Chandler?
Yeah!
Hi.
So how are things going
with Crazy?
Has she cooked
your rabbit yet?
Listen, you are hearing
one side of the story.
And FYI, she must
have shown Kyle
over 30 paint samples
before she painted
that room.
And his response
to each one was,
"I don't give a tiny rat's ass."
Yeah, well, maybe
she should have spent
a little less time
decorating
and a little more
time in the bedroom.
Well, I don't think we
are going to have that problem
but maybe that's
just because I am not
emotionally unavailable.
You think he's
emotionally unavailable?
I think he can be.
Well, maybe he wouldn't be
if she didn't bring
the office home
with her every night.
Well, excuse her for knowing
what she wants to do
with her life.
Yeah, well, she certainly
knew what she was doing
New Year's Eve 1997.
I knew you were going
to throw that in my face.
That was three years ago.
She apologized
and apologized.
What more do you want?!
We want the last six years back!
So do we! So do we!
I'm sorry you had
to see that.
Morning, Rachel.
Hi.
Hey, so what'd
you do last night?
Went out with Joey.
Oh, yeah?
Another night
of bird-dogging the chicas?
No. We had a really good talk.
I don't think
I'm going
to do that bar scene anymore.
Wow. I did not see that coming.
It's just not really who I am.
You know, I've always
been happier when...
Why am I telling you this?
You don't care
about this stuff.
Yes, I do, I do.
Tell me...
Go on. You were saying
"I am happier when I'm..."
When I'm in a relationship.
I love having a girlfriend.
Really?
Yeah. Someone I can spoil,
you know?
Spoil?
Uh-huh.
Let me ask
you something.
Uh-huh.
Do you believe there's
one perfect person
for everyone?
I-I'm starting to.
If that person's
already in your life
you should do something
about it, right?
Yes. Hell, yes.
All right, then,
it's settled.
Okay.
I'm getting back together
with my ex-girlfriend.
I would love to.
What?
Hello?
Oh, yeah...
This is going
to be a while.
Excuse me.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yuck!
( spoon clanking )
My God!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is that annoying?
Oh, and speaking of being
selfish in bed, how's Whitney?
Well, maybe she wouldn't have
to be selfish in bed
if someone else knew
where everything was.
Oh, he knows.
For the most part.
Oh, hey.
Good, you're
both here.
We kind of need
to talk.
Both of you together?
What's up?
Well, I went over
to Kyle's last night
to pick up
a few things
and... we got
to reminiscing.
Kyle:
We talked through
most of the night
and we realized
that the reason
we're so angry
with each other
is because there's still
feelings there.
So...
Oh, just say it, Kyle!
We're going to give it
another try.
What about her whining
and her constant need
for attention?
I'm going to work
on that.
Oh, right, 'cause you're
so capable of change.
You know, he hums
when he pees.
I do know.
Makes him miss the bowl,
but whatever.
We're so sorry.
Ross:
That's all right.
We don't need you.
In fact, I'm over it already.
And you know what?
I don't even give
a tiny rat's ass.
Yeah. We're
going to go.
I'm sorry.
Pheebs, you were
right about her.
You know, she did try
to use sex as a weapon.
I hurt my back
a little.
You know, he hums while
he does other stuff, too.
Yeah, we're better
off without them.
And you know
even if they
break up again
you better not let him
in your Sad Men's Club.
Divorced Men's Club.
Potato, Potahto.
Hey, guys, check it out.
My mom sent me
the paper.
Ooh, let's see it.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, that looks good.
You guys make
a very attractive couple.
Yeah, we look
great together.
We really do.
Okay.
Imagine what our kids
would look like.
You know, we don't have
to imagine.
I'm marrying her.
We'll just see.